Guide to the Livingston Farrand papers, 1921-1939.
Farrand, Livingston Papers
- STATE Miscellaneous., 1922-26 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  New York State Board of Charities.
- STATE-STE Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  Stcherbinsky, Serge.
- STE-STEE Miscellaneous., 1921-31 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  Hart, Merwin K.; Stcherbinsky, Serge.
- STEE-STEPH Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  Steunke, John Jacob.
- STEPH-STER Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  Stephenson, Carl; Hiscock, Frank H.; Graves, Frank Pierrepont; Sternheim, Emanuel; Ramsey, William.
- STER-STEU Miscellaneous., 1925-33 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  Ramsey, William.
- State Scholarships., 1930-32 (Box 34, Folder 60)
- Stevens Miscellaneous., 1919-37 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  Stevens, Robert S. Law School.
- Stevens-STEW Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  Stevenson, Howard A.; Stevenson, J. R.; Palmer, Archie M. Cornell Alumni News.
- Stewart Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  Stewart, George B.
- Stewart-STIM Miscellaneous., 1928-34 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  Stiles, Wallace C.; Matheson, Robert.
- STIM-STOCK Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  Stimson, Lewis A.; Stock, A.
- STOCK-Stone Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Stocking, William A.
- Stone-STOR Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  Storey, Thomas A. Presidents' Committee of Fifty on College Hygiene.
- STOR Miscellaneous., 1922-27 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  Storey, Thomas A.
- STOR-STOW Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Straight Miscellaneous., 1908-36 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  Straight, Willard D.; Straight, Henry H.; Schurman, Jacob Gould.
- Straight, Willard D., 1914-19 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  Straight, Dorothy.
- Straight, Willard (Mrs. )., 1919-31 (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
  Straight, Dorothy; Mann, Albert R.; Garr, Llewellyn; Straight, Willard D.
- Street-Strong Miscellaneous., 1902-35 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  Strickler, Daniel B.
- Strong-Strunk., 1925-33 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  Strunk, William; Strong, Harold F.; Strunk, Catherine.
- Strunk, William., 1923-35 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Strunk, William-Student Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  Stuart, Kenneth E. Student Council.
- Student Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 35, Folder 19-20)
  Student Council.
- Student-Stutz Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  Stull, C. Rodman. Student Friendship Fund; Students International Union.
- Stutz-Styles Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  Stutz, Harry G.; Styles, Flora N.; Skeats, Wilfred S.
- SUA-SUMM Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  Sulgrave Institution.
- Summer Session. Summers, Harry A.; Petry, Loren C., 1925-34 (Box 35, Folder 24-26)
- Summer Session-SUMN Miscellaneous., 1928-32 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  Sumner, James B.
- SUN-SUND Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  Sunderville, Earl. New York State Veterinary College.
- SUND-SUR Miscellaneous., 1921-31 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  Surette, Thomas Whitney; Sunderville, Earl. New York State Veterinary College.
- SUR-SUTH Miscellaneous. Survey Associates., 1921-36 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- SUTH-SUZZ Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  Allen, Arthur A.; Suzzalo, Henry.
- SWA-SWE Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  Swarthmore College; John Edson Sweet Professorship of Engineering.
- SWE-SWI Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  Sweetser, Arthur; Young, Charles V. P. League of Nations Health Committee.
- SWI Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  Switzer, F. G.
- SY-SYR Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  Symons, Josephine.
- Syracuse, New York., 1922-34 (Box 35, Folder 36-38)
  Flint, Charles W. Syracuse University.
- Syracuse-SZ Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  Sze, Sao-ke Alfred.
- TAB-TAG Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  Taft, William Howard.
- TAG-TAL Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  Tagawa, B.
- TALL-TAN Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  Tanner, J. H.
- TANN-TAO Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  Tanner, J. H.; Tansey, George J.
- TAPP-TAU Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  Tarbell, George S.
- TAU-TAY Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  Taussig, Charles A. Taxation.
- Taylor Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 35, Folder 46)
- Taylor, Myron C., 1926-34 (Box 35, Folder 47-49)
  Myron Taylor C. Hall; Law School.
- Taylor, Myron C. -Taylor, W., 1924-33 (Box 35, Folder 50)
- Teachers., 1920-37 (Box 35, Folder 51-52)
  Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association.
- Teagle, Walter C., 1926-37 (Box 35, Folder 53-57)
- TEEP-TEN Miscellaneous., 1925-29 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  Johnson, E. M. Telluride Association.
- TEN-TENN Miscellaneous. Ten Eyck, Peter G. New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets., 1921-37 (Box 35, Folder 59)
- TERR-Texas Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  Texas Company.
- THA-THAT Miscellaneous., 1922-27 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  Thatcher, R. W. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.
- THAT Miscellaneous., 1925 (Box 35, Folder 62)
- THAT-THEO Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Thatcher, R. W.; Butler, Nicholas Murray. New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Union Theological Seminary.
- THEO-Theta Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  Theological seminaries
- THI-Thilly Miscellaneous., 1928-35 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Thilly, Frank.
- Thilly, Frank., 1923-27 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- THIN-THOM Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation.
- THOM Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  Thompson, George J.; Thompson, W. 0. Law School; Ohio State University.
- THOR-THUR Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  Thorndike, E. L.
- THUR-THWI Miscellaneous., 1922-28 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  Thurber, Charles H.
- TOB-TOLL Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  Tokimasa, David; Onda, Tsunehichi; Ushizukas, Torataro.
- TOM-TOMP Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  Tomlinson, F. C. Nutrimine.
- TOMP-TOMS Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  Toms, S. W. S. Tompkins County Memorial Hospital.
- TOMS-TOR Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  Toms, S. W. S.; Mead, Robert G. (Mrs. ) Siam; University of Toronto.
- TOR-TOW Miscellaneous., 1920-33 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  Tout, T. F.; Towle, John W. University of Toronto; Fraternities.
- TOW-TRA Miscellaneous., 1922-28 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  Towle, John W.; Kerr, Abram T. Town and Gown Club; Committee on Traffic Control.
- Committee on Traffic Control., 1924-34 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  Traxel, Emma J. Fellowship of Youth for Peace.
- Treman, Charles E., 1925-30 (Box 36, Folder 17-18)
  Treman, Arthur B.; Treman, Allan H.
- Treman, Robert E., 1926-37 (Box 36, Folder 19-21)
  Boak, Thomas I. S.
- Treman, Robert H., 1921-35 (Box 36, Folder 22-26)
- Treman, Robert E., 1926-36 (Box 36, Folder 27-30)
  Wagner, Hans. War Memorial.
- TREV-TROP Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  Trevor, Joseph Ellis.
- TROP-TRUS Miscellaneous., 1926-35 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  Trousdale, J. B.; Truman, James S. Office of the Auditor.
- TRUS Miscellaneous., 1932-37 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  Lynah, James; Curtis, Ralph W. Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics; Arboretum.
- Board of Trustees., 1922-35 (Box 36, Folder 34-35)
  Upson, Maxwell M. Alumni Corporation.
- Trustees-TUCK Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  Tsar, F. Y.; Tsai, T. T. Planning Commission.
- Tuition-Faculty Children., 1922-32 (Box 36, Folder 37-44)
- Tuition-Faculty Children., 1933-37 (Box 36, Folder 45-49)
- Tuition., 1924-37 (Box 36, Folder 50-57)
- TUK-TUS Miscellaneous., 1929-35 (Box 36, Folder 58)
  Tuskegee Institute.
- TUS-TWE Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Tweedy, Henry H.
- TWEN-TZ Miscellaneous., 1927-33 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- UC-UN Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  Fox, Dixon Ryan. Union College.
- UN-US Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Union College; ROTC.
- US Miscellaneous., 1922-25 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  United States Marine Corps; United States Naval Academy; Cornell Widow.
- U. S. S. R. -USV Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  Delinski, Bernard.
- Unemployment., 1931-33 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
  New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration.
- Universal-University Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  Treman, Robert H. University Club.
- Committee on University Lectures., 1933-37 (Box 37, Folder 10-14)
  Bishop, Morris G.; Sapir, Edward; Cunningham, G. Watts. Goldwin Smith Foundation; Schiff Foundation.
- University T-Ups Miscellaneous. Upson, Maxwell M. University Travel Association., 1927-33 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Upson Miscellaneous. Upson, Maxwell M., 1921-35 (Box 37, Folder 16-17)
- UPT-UW Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  Morris, Ellis.
- VAC-VAN Miscellaneous. Vail, Roger Sherman; Valentine, Alan; Debs, Eugene V.; Van Auken, M. W. Vaccination., 1925-37 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Van Cleef, Mynderse., 1921-35 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  Gage, Simon Henry.
- Van Cleef-Van N Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  Van Cleef, Mynderse.
- Van N-VANN Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  Van Namee, George R.; Vanneman, C. Reeve.
- Van Blarcom, Conant. Dept. of Buildings and Grounds., 1926-36 (Box 37, Folder 23-24)
- Van O-Van R Miscellaneous., 1930-35 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  Martha Van Rensselaer Hall.
- Van Rensselaer, Martha., 1923-33 (Box 37, Folder 26-28)
- Van S-VEL Miscellaneous., 1919-35 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- VEL-VIZ Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- VIZ-VONE Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  Chardon, Carlos E.; von Engeln, O. D. Porto Rico.
- VONE-VONS Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  von Engeln, O. D. Dept. of Geology.
- VONS-WAC Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- New York State Veterinary College Deanship., 1922-36 (Box 37, Folder 34-36)
- WAD-WAG Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  Wadsworth, Eliot; Wadsworth, James W.
- WAG-WAK Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  Wagner, Robert F.
- WAX Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  Wakeman, S. W.
- WAL Miscellaneous., 1927-31 (Box 37, Folder 40)
- WALK Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  McMullen Scholarships.
- WALK-WALL Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  Wallace, Henry.
- WALL-WALT Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  Mann, Albert R.
- WALT Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  Walter, Richard 0.
- WALZ-WARD Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- WARD-WARN Miscellaneous., 1928-35 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- WARN-WARR Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  Warren, George F.
- WARR Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 37, Folder 48)
- WARR-WARW Miscellaneous. Warren, George F., 1922-28 (Box 37, Folder 49)
- United States War Department., 1921-28 (Box 37, Folder 50-54)
  Ely, H. E. ROTC.
- United States War Department., 1929-30 (Box 37, Folder 55-58)
  Nolan, D. E.
- War Memorial at Cornell., 1931 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
  Wagner, Hans.
- Robert Boyd Ward Fund., 1926-34 (Box 38, Folder 4-7)
- WASH Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 38, Folder 8-10)
  Peaslee, Horace W.; Washington, George. Washington and Jefferson College.
- WASH-WAT Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  Washington University.
- WAT-WAY Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Weaver, Paul J., 1928-37 (Box 38, Folder 13-17)
  Dept. of Music.
- WE-WEB Miscellaneous., 1926-37 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  Weagant, Carl; Weber, Rudolph.
- WEB-WEI Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  Weeks, Archibald C.
- Weil, A. D., 1924-33 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  University of Strasbourg; University of Paris; University of Brussels; Cornell Alumni Association in France.
- Weil, A. D. -WEIN Miscellaneous., 1927-32 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  American University Union in Europe; University of Caen.
- WEIN-WEL Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- WELD-WELL Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  Weld, H. P.; Welling, Richard. Wells College.
- WELL-WES Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  Wentworth, Harold. Wells College.
- WES-WEST Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  West, James E.
- WEST Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- WESTE Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- WESTE-WESTI Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  Westervelt, John Corley; Westinghouse, Henry.
- WESTI-WESTM Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  Westinghouse, Henry.
- WESTM-Weyl Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  Weyl, James Sailer.
- WHA-WHET Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  Wheeler, Benjamin Ide; Whetzel, H. H.
- WHET-WHIT Miscellaneous., 1920-35 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  Whetzel, H. H.; Hamilton Holt; Whinery, Andrew J. Committee on Student Conduct; University of Porto Rico.
- WHIT-White, Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  Whitcomb, Anna Gauntlett; White, Andrew C.; White, Helen Magill; White, Andrew Dickson.
- White Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 38, Folder 34-35)
  White, E. A.; White, Georgia L.
- White, Horatio S., 1921-32 (Box 38, Folder 36-37)
  White, J. Dupratt; Taylor, Myron C. Icelandic Collection.
- White, J. Dupratt., 1922-35 (Box 38, Folder 38-53)
  Hiscock, Frank H. Board of Trustees; Military training; Cornell University Medical College; Student housing; Myron Taylor Hall; Prudential Insurance Company; Alumni Fields; Cornellian Council.
- White, J. Dupratt., 1926-28 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
  White, Helen Magill.
- White, J. Dupratt., 1935-37 (Box 39, Folder 3-8)
  Bostwick, Charles D.; Hiscock, Frank H.
- White Miscellaneous., 1929-33 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- WHITM-WHO Miscellaneous., 1932-37 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  Whitman, Ezra B.; Whitney, Payne.
- WID-WIE Miscellaneous., 1927-33 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  Wiegand, Karl M. Summer School of Biology.
- WIE-WIG Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  Wiggans, R. G.
- WILB-WILK Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  Wilbur, Ray Lyman; Wilder, Burt Green; Kerr, Abram T.; Gabrielson, Ira N.
- Willard Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  Sze, Sao-ke Alfred. Willard Straight Memorial Scholarship.
- Willard Straight Hall., 1922-34 (Box 39, Folder 15-20)
- Williams, Roger H., 1927-37 (Box 39, Folder 21-22)
  Board of Trustees Finance Committee.
- Willcox Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 39, Folder 23-24)
  Willcox, Walter F.; Willcox, William B.
- WILLE-WILLI Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  Dennis, L. M.; William, Maurice; Williams, Bruce.
- Williams Miscellaneous., 1923-26 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  Williams College.
- Williams-Willis, E. R. B., 1922-37 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Willis, E. R. B. -WILLS Miscellaneous., 1927-30 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  Cornell University Library.
- Wilson Miscellaneous., 1930-34 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  Wilson, Ellwood.
- Wilson Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  Wilson, Lyman P.; Wilson, Woodrow.
- WIN-WINS Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  Wing, Henry Hiram.
- WINS-WISE Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  Winslow, Floyd S.
- WOE-WOM Miscellaneous., 1925-34 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  Wolkinson, Herman.
- WOM-WOO Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  Women's Self-Government Association.
- WOOD-WOOT Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  Woodward, B. D.
- WOR Miscellaneous., 1927-36 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  Wordsworth, Gordon Graham. Wordsworth Collection; New York State Works Progress Administration; World Agriculture Society.
- WOR-WRI Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  Ickes, Harold L.; Wright, Henry C.; Mann, Albert R.; Wright, Ivan.
- WRI Miscellaneous., 1921-22 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  Wright, Ivan.
- WRI-WY Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  Wright, Louis B.; Farrand, Max.
- WY-X Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- YA-YOR Miscellaneous., 1925-33 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  York, Edward P. Yale University Press.
- Young, George Jr., 1925-37 (Box 39, Folder 42-46)
  Clarke, Gilmore D. College of Architecture; City and regional planning.
- Young Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  Young, Charles V. P. Dept. of Physical Education.
- Young-YM Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  Young, Charles V. P.; Young, Owen D. Dept. of Physical Education; National Collegiate Athletic Association.
- ZA-ZUR Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  University of Zurich.
- Puerto (Porto) Rico., 1927-32 (Box 39, Folder 50-57)
  Chardon, Carlos E.; Roosevelt, Theodore; Van Cleef, Mynderse; White, J. Dupratt; Benner, Thomas E. University of Porto Rico.
- Congratulatory Letters and Messages., 1921-23 (Box 40, Folder 1-16)
- Farrand Inauguration Miscellaneous., 1921 (Box 40, Folder 17-29)
- Farrand Inauguration and Personal Papers., 1921 (Box 40, Folder 31-33)
- Farrand Speeches., 1921-31 (Box 40, Folder 34-47)
  Folders were misnumbered, there is no folder 42
- Farrand Miscellaneous., 1921-39 (Box 40, Folder 48-52)
- Letters of Condolence., 1939-40 (Box 40, Folder 53-65)
- Memorium., 1940 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Letters of Condolence., 1939 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook., 1921-22 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence-Mrs. Farrand., 1939 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Photographs., n. d. (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Ithaca Journal, Oct. 20., 1921 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Democrat and Chronicle (Rochester), Oct. 21., 1921 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Cornell Daily Sun, Oct. 21., 1921 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- The Post Standard, Oct. 20., 1921 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Cornell Daily Sun, Oct. 20., 1921 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Photographs., n. d. (Box 42, Folder 7-10)
- Red Cross Scrapbook., 1918-19 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Oversize Documents, Brochures, and Diplomas., n. d. (Box 43)
- American Red Cross portfolio, 1918-11-1919-4; Hine, Lewis Wickes, 1874-1940; American Red Cross; 20.3 x 25.4 cm; Single portfolio containing 19 photographs (Box 44)
  This portfolio contains photographic prints created by Lewis W. Hine for Lt. Colonel Homer Folks during a survey mission for the American Red Cross. Photographs document refugees, camps, and relief efforts in France, Serbia, and Greece.
  American Red Cross
  Serbia
  Greece
  France
  World War, 1914-1918
  Refugees
  Humanitarian assistance
  Gelatin silver prints